<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<pageData>
  <pageLayout><![CDATA[{"ay__middlebar0":"pageEditText","ay__middlebar0editable":"<h2>Billing Policy <\/h2>\n<h6>The following Terms of Use constitute our Billing Policy and apply to ALL  customers:<\/h6>\n\n<h6>Payments<\/h6>\n<p>\nAll charges are shown in US Dollars. Payments are to be made in US dollars and must be drawn from a US bank. We accepts the following types of payment:<\/p>\n<p>\n   <a href=\"#\">Check or Money Order<\/a><br>\n   <a href=\"#\">Google Checkout<\/a><br>\n\n    <a href=\"#\">Credit Card (VISA, MasterCard, Discover)<\/a><br>\n        <a href=\"#\">PayPal<\/a><\/p>\n\t\t<p>\n\nAll payments are due on the Account Statement Date. The Account Statement Date is the monthly anniversary of the date the account was activated. If you provide us your credit card information, you authorize us to automatically charge your credit or debit card for charges that apply to your account. Recurring charges will be posted to your credit card until such time that you cancel your account in accordance with our Billing Policy in the TOU. You are responsible for directly updating, or notifying us, of any changes to your credit card (including, but not limited to card number, expiration date, billing address, or card status).<\/p>\n<p>\n\nCustomers not paying by credit card agree to make payment of their balance due within ten (10) days of the Account Statement Date.<\/p>\n\n<p>\n\nAccounts that are thirty (30) days past due will be automatically suspended. All past due and unpaid balances are subject to collection. In the event of collection, you will be liable for costs of collection including attorney's fees, court costs, and collection agency fees.<\/p>\n<h6>Account Renewals<\/h6>\n            <p> In order to insure uninterrupted service to your website, all \n              plans will automatically renew at the end of the plan's billing \n              cycle. Plan renewal charges are based on the original rate on the \n              date of renewal according to the service selected. Plans are renewed \n              for the same billing cycle term. If you wish to cancel your plan \n              before the plan renewal, please refer to the cancellation section \n              below. An automated renewal notification will be sent to the email \n              address on the account, at least 30 days prior to actual processing \n              of the renewal. From time to time, we may avail ourself \n              of account updating services provided by the Payment Card Industry, \n              including, without limitation, VISA's Account Updater program or \n              MasterCard's Automatic Billing Updater program. By subscribing to \n              our premium service, you hereby agree and authorize us \n              to update your Payment Card or similar account information and charge \n              any updated Payment Card in accordance with the terms and conditions \n              of such account updating programs. Coupons can not be used for renewals, \n              and only apply to new customers.<\/p>\n<h6>\n\nImportant Notice<\/h6>\n<h6>Statements<\/h6>\n<p>\n\nWe do not mail paper invoices or statements. Statements can be viewed and printed through the billing control panel.<\/p>\n\n<h6>Fees<\/h6>\n<a href=\"#\">\n    Returned (NSF) Checks<\/a>\n\n    <p>We charge a $25.00 fee for returned (NSF) checks. Customers that issue an NSF check will be required to submit future payments with a certified check or money order.<\/p>\n   <a href=\"#\"> Processing Fees<\/a>\n<p>    A $50 - $100 fee will be assessed for each processing fee for illegal transactions.<\/p>\n\n<h6>\n\nCancellations<\/h6>\n\n<h6>30-Day Money Back Guarantee\n<\/h6>\n\n<p>Each of our online services carries a 30-day unconditional money back guarantee. If you are not completely satisfied with our services or support within the first 30 days, you will be given a full refund. The following services do not qualify for the 30 Day Money Back Guarantee: account renewals, additional items and services and domain name registration.<\/p>\n<h6>\nBilling\/Price Changes<\/h6>\n<p>Our policies and prices are subject to change without notice. Any price changes become effective in the next billing cycle.<\/p> <br>\n<h6><\/h6>","ay__middlebar0_parameters":"editable","ay__rightbar0":"menuView","ay__rightbar0editable":"View a Menu","ay__rightbar0_parameters":"editable,option","ay__rightbar0option":"terms_and_policies"}]]></pageLayout>
</pageData>
